

MAARTEN HORMES

BASC. SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PERSONAL INFORMATION

E-mail: maarten.hormes@gmail.com Phone number: +31 6 18687280

Address: Karel Doormanstraat 3c 6045EA Roermond

Date of birth: 27-01- 2000



LinkedIn



GitHub link



Portfolio site

ABOUT ME

Hello there, I am a full-stack software engineer Limax B.V. Here I develop software for our in-house ERP. I've become a software engineering, due to my interest in writing software since high school. After starting my studies, this interest has turned into a hobby and personal need to understand, know more and get better at what I like doing.

I am a social person, a team player, goal-oriented and very structured. I like to get things done, properly! Structure makes a developers life easier, thats why I love it so much. I am always open to converse and share views in order to find the most suitable solution or approach for each situation.

With just half a decade of experience, I am able to understand complex concepts due to my habit of always wanting to know more and my willingness to have a open conversation about a wide range of topics (both IT and non-IT related).

EDUCATION

2020 - 2024 Fontys ICT & software engineering, Engllish stream, Eindhoven

Graduate of the software engineering course at Fontys University of Applied Science. With a specialization in creative technology (develop tech in a creative way with focus on helping society). Minoring in Embrace TEC (technology, entrepreneurship & creativity), to discover my passion in IT and define who I am as a professional.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Limax B.V., Horst (full-time) Aug 2024 - present

Full-stack software engineer

• After graduation, I got offered a full-time contract at Limax B.V. where I continue to work as a full-stack software engineer of the Flowcontrol system. Besides starting as a full-stack Software Engineer, I am also responsible for the management of our hosted applications, the security specialist and part of the small team setting up the IT department.

Quad Solutions, Eindhoven (graduation internship) Feb 2024 - July 2024

Junior software engineer

My graudation internship was performed at Quad Solutions in Eindhoven. During my graudation I worked on the
development of a web application for the company. This application integrated with the company's hour booking
system and was intended to be used by management to verify logged hours, analyze over- & under-booking and
creacte projections for contract periods. The project consists of a SpringBoot backend and a React.js frontend,
being hosted on Heroku and Vercel respectively.

Limax B.V., Horst (part-time)

Feb 2023 - July 2024

Junior software engineer

• After a successfull internship, I got offered a job to stay and work as a full stack web developer at the company. Here I continued working on the development of the Flowcontrol system.

Limax B.V., Horst (internship)

Aug 2022 - Jan 2023

Software engineer intern

• My first internship was performed at Limax B.V. where I worked on the development of the Flowcontrol system. Here I was tasked to create a security implementation to secure the system. This included the implementation of a OAuth2.0 provider (Keycloak), a JWT token system and RBAC configuration.

DEYO Huiswerkbegeleiding, Roermond (part-time)

Apr 2022 - Feb 2023

• Tutored in Dutch and math.

LANGUAGES

Dutch Native Language
English Fluent
German Average

HOBBY'S

Football/Sports

Music (technical side of music as well as playing the guitar/singing)

Software development

Esports

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Developed in:

- C#
- Java (Spring)
- JavaScript (React.js / Vue.js)
- TypeScript

Worked with:

- Git (GitHub/GitLab)
- Docker
- Keycloak
- Postman
- Sonarqube
- Podman
- Heroku
- Vercel
- Render

SOFT SKILLS

Professional skills:

- Structured
- Orderly
- Result driven
- Team player

Personal skills:

- Passionate
- Tidy
- Communicative
- Independent